<resources>
    <string name="app_name">HeyNotes</string>
    <string name="app_version">v0.1.9</string>

    <string name="app_description">HeyNotes is your minimal, distraction-free space for thoughts, ideas, and plans.
     It is designed to be fast, local and private when needed. All notes you create can be located under Internal
        Storage > Documents > HeyNotes. This allows you to bring in your previous .md files from any other app you currently use,
        and export them from this app when you need it.</string>

    <!-- FIXED: Added backslash to phone\'s -->
    <string name="app_privacy_info">Secure Folders are hidden from your phone\'s File Manager and exist in a protected storage
        area accessible only by this app. Be careful: If you delete a Secure Folder, all notes inside it are permanently
        deleted and cannot be recovered. </string>

    <string name="app_github_link">https://github.com/GhostyApps/</string>

    <!-- UI Strings -->
    <string name="important_warning">⚠️ Important: No PIN Recovery</string>
    <string name="secure_instructions">1. Find the "Private" folder in your list.\n2. Tap it to set up your 4 or 6-digit PIN.\n3. Notes created here are encrypted locally.</string>


    <string name="how_to_get_key_title">How to get Gemini API Key?</string>
    <string name="how_to_get_key_desc">
        1. Go to &lt;a href=\"https://aistudio.google.com/app/apikey\"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Google AI Studio - API Key&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; page.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
        2. Click the &lt;b&gt;\"Create API key\"&lt;/b&gt; button.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
        3. You will be asked to select a project. You can choose an existing one or create a new project such as \"HeyNotes\".&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
        4. Give a name to your key (e.g., \"HeyNotes\"). Unique names will help you easily track usage statistics later.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
        5. Once created, copy the key from the list and paste it into the field above.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
        &lt;b&gt;Usage Limits:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
        HeyNotes is powered by the &lt;b&gt;Gemini 3.0 Flash Preview&lt;/b&gt; model. The current free quota allows for approximately &lt;b&gt;1000 audio analyses per day&lt;/b&gt;. Please note that these limits are subject to change according to Google\'s policies.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
        &lt;small&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;Disclaimer:&lt;/b&gt; This application utilizes the Gemini AI API to provide transcription services but is independently developed and is not affiliated with, endorsed by, or connected to Google LLC.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/small&gt;
    </string>


</resources>